// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1, 	
  question: "Muslims will often write the initials P.B.U.H. after the name of a prophet. What does this mean?",
  answer: "Peace be upon him",
  options: [  
      "Please be utterly happy",
      "Peace be upon him", 
      "Peace be under heaven", 
      "Peace be up high"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 2, 	
  question: "In which direction do Muslims face when praying?",
  answer: "Towards Mecca",
  options: [
    "Towards Mecca",
    "Towards Istanbul",
    "Towards Rome",
    "Towards Jerusalem"
  ]
  
},
{
  numb: 3, 
  question: "The name Islam comes from the word 'Salaam', which means .......",
  answer: "peace",
  options: [	
     "love",
     "freedom",
     "peace",
     "justice"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 4, 
  question: "The holy month of prayer, fasting and pilgrimage is known as .......",
  answer: "Ramadan",
  options: [
    "Spring",
    "Eid",
    "Ramadan",
    "Shahadah"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 5, 
  question: "How many times a day should Muslims pray?",
  answer: "Five times",
  options: [
     "Once",
     "Twice",
     "Four times",
     "Five times"
  ]
 },
{
  numb: 6, 
  question: "Which of the following is NOT a holy and sacred book in Islam?",
  answer: "De Anima", 
  options: [
       "The Koran",
       "The Psalms",
       "The Bible",
       "De Anima"
  ]
  
},
{
  numb: 7, 
  question: "Where do Muslims go to worship?",
  answer: "A mosque",
  options: [
     "A temple",
     "A church",
     "A synagogue",
     "A mosque"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "How many pillars of Islam are there?",
  answer: "Five",
  options: [
     "Four",
     "Five",
     "Eight", 
     "Ten"
  ]

},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "One of the pillars of Islam is Salah, which means .......",
  answer: "prayer",
  options: [
    "prayer",
    "fasting", 
    "giving to charity",
    "pilgrimage"
  ]
 
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "What is the name for the pilgrimage to Mecca which all faithful Muslims must try to undertake at least once?",
  answer: "Hajj",
  options: [
    "Shahadah", 
    "Salah",
    "Hajj",
    "Zakah"
  ]
  
},
];